

Phone:

+49 (0)176 4763 6041

Location:

München, Germany

Email:

talandarko@gmail.com

LinkedIn:

linkedin.com/in/darkotalangp9/

Skills

- □ HTML & CSS
- JavaScript
- React
- Bootstrap
- Express.js
- Node.js
- MongoDb
- SQL

Languages

Croatian – native speaker English – C1 German – C1

Courses

- Microsoft SQL Database Development
- Programming basics with Java
- Project management IPMA® Level D
- Agile Project management with Scrum® -PSM I

Junior Full Stack Web Developer with 15 years experience in tourism management who recently graduated from a 1-year intensive training in Full Stack Web Development. Seeking a position to apply experience gained as a team player, servant, and mentor in the hospitality and entertainment business to challenge me and deliver solutions-oriented approaches.

Education

Full Stack Web Development at DCI - Digital Career Institute gGmbH, Berlin

September 2020 - October 2021

- Accomplishing a one-year-full-time training including technologies from MERN stack
- → Completing multiple small and one final large practical project to practice programming skills
- → Taking German lessons as part of the course with a certificate in Level C1-Beruf

Master of Economics at Tourism and Hospitality Management

- University of Rijeka, Croatia

October 2003 - October 2013

Work history

Front and Back Office Agent in Hospitality at Design Hotel Stadt Rosenheim and H-Hotels.com GmbH September 2017 - May 2019

- Perfected in customer care and service
- Managed sales and reservations
- → Handled customer complaints professionally

Assistant Casino Manager and Unit Manager at Gogs Gambling and Casinos Ltd, Zagreb, Croatia

September 2017 - May 2019

- Oversaw employee activities and created scheduling charts.
- Assisted with the screening of new recruits. Trained and mentored new employees.
- → Scheduled shift and resolved customer issues.